forumgrad.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Lean more about Business News, Technology trends, Fashion Tips and all trending Topics

Thank you for visiting ForumGrad.com, a business-news website owned by ForumGrad. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this ForumGrad site.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page. Check back often, as continued access of the website by you will constitute your acceptance of any revisions to the Privacy Policy.

If you object to any terms and conditions of the Privacy Policy at any time, you should immediately discontinue use of the site.

**Users of ForumGrad.com  
**

ForumGrad.com does not sell, rent, give away or loan any identifiable information regarding its members to any third party without the user’s consent, except as required by law, or as noted below.

Participation in submitting information to our Calendar of Events, On the Job, Briefcase or other editorial compilations requires that information be made available within the context of the website and our print editions. Submission of research information for our lists and directories, such as the Book of List publications, medical directories, technology directories, etc., requires that information be made available to individuals purchasing the Book of Lists or directory products online.

In order to subscribe to our daily and weekly email newsletters, provide ForumGrad with feedback, make advertising requests, or receive email updates, users are required to provide us with their email address.

The information we collect may be used by us to contact users for marketing purposes, including via email, mail, telephone or social media.

ForumGrad.com will not disclose any of your specific personal information unless you consent to disclose it. If you elect to participate in a special program, your specific personal information may be shared with participating vendors in order to complete the transaction.

Online, or through other means of contact, when you subscribe, register, make purchases, submit surveys or at other times, we collect and store personally identifiable information from you that may include your name; your postal and email addresses; facts about your profession, company and responsibilities; and information regarding your computer system that may be passed on to an approved third party for storage and payment processing.This list is subject to change. Please contact us for an updated list or with questions regarding the information shared with these third parties. Information collected about subscribers and users may be used by us and our affiliates to provide subscribers and users with the features of the site, to enable us to provide the products you requested, to personalize content and advertising, to send you email notifications about our services and products, for audits, to perform statistical analysis of user behavior in order to measure interest in the various areas of our site (such as for product development purposes), to enforce our user agreement, and to inform advertisers as to how many users have seen or “clicked” their advertising banners. We will disclose site usage information to third parties only in aggregate.

For each visitor to this website, our Web server may automatically attempt to identify the user through a cookie set within your browser. This is done to provide access to the site.

If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us update your subscription preferences here or submit a request to be removed from our email database by completing the form found here [Feedback form link].

If you supply us with your telephone number and postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please notify us through the email address or telephone number listed below.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us regarding orders they have placed online.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated purposes not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes. With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server. Visitors may verify their security status by looking for the https:// portion of the URL in their browser or by calling us to verify the safety of their information.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the Forum Grad online policy for this site or its implementation, you may email us here or write to the following address:

**Forum Grad**

3407 Dewy Inlet,  
Hasty,  
New York,  
11146-8866,  
US
